Long John Nebel Papers
Long John Nebel Papers
- Tapes
  - LJN All Night Show
    - "Theology" (repeated 1968 March 3) Harvey Cox, Robert Cochnar, Will Ousler, Sanford Teller, December 29, 1967; nebel_0979-0981; 3 reels (Oversize 49)
    - Pat Cooper, Al Lottman, Danny Crystal, Al Reyes, Dennis Brite, December 30, 1967; nebel_0982-0984; 3 reels (Oversize 49)
    - "Freud" Dr. Hanna Kapit, Sanford Teller, Dennis Brite, December 31, 1967; nebel_0985-0987; 3 reels (Oversize 49)
    - "Mark, I Love You" Hal Painter, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Terry Garrity, January 4, 1968; nebel_0988-0989; 2 reels (Oversize 49, 50)
    - Dr. Carlton Fredericks, Seena Hamilton, Terry Garrity, January 6, 1968; nebel_0995-0996; 2 reels (Oversize 50)
    - Dr. Erika Freeman, Seena Hamilton, Terry Garrity, Rev. Robert Schlock, January 7, 1968; nebel_0997-1000; 4 reels (Oversize 50)
    - Norman Mailer, Sanford Teller, Robert Cochnar, January 10, 1968; nebel_1006-1007; 2 reels (Oversize 50)
    - "Reason And Emotion In Psychotherapy" (repeated 1968 June 9) Dr. Albert Ellis, Seena Hamilton, Terry Garrity, January 14, 1968; nebel_1012-1015; 4 reels (Oversize 50, 51)
    - "21st Century" Edward Wardwell, Scott MacLeod, Lester Del Rey, Frederik Pohl, January 17, 1968; nebel_1021-1023; 3 reels (Oversize 51)
    - "The Innocent Consumer" Sidney Margolis, Terry Garrity, Robert Schrock, Alan Cornet, January 18, 1968; nebel_1026-1028; 3 reels (Oversize 51)
    - "Beyond Success And Failure" (aired 1968 May 12) Marguerite Beecher, Willard Beecher, Seena Hamilton, Dr. Hanna Kapit, January 19, 1968; nebel_1030-1032; 3 reels (Oversize 51, 52)
    - Jean Shepherd, Sanford Teller, Bob Cochnar, January 20, 1968; nebel_1034-1036; 3 reels (Oversize 52)
    - "Death Row" Richard Plechner, January 29, 1968; nebel_1048; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 52)
    - "Mouse Power" James Moran reel, January 29, 1968; nebel_1049; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 52)
    - "Guide To Developing Your Potential" Dr. Herbert Otto, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Seena Hamilton, Terry Garrity, January 30, 1968; nebel_1050-1052; 3 reels (Oversize 52)
    - "Edgar Cayce On Reincarnation" (repeated 1968 June 30) Hugh L. Cayce, Will Ousler, Roy Schatt, Samuel Vandervirt, January 31, 1968; nebel_1055-1057; 3 reels (Oversize 53)
    - "The Lawbreakers" (aired 1968 March 17) M. Stanton Evans, David A. Schulte, Al Lottman, Seena Hamilton, February 2, 1968; nebel_1061-1063; 3 reels (Oversize 53)
    - "Animal Kitabu" (repeated 1968 April 21) Jean-Pierre Hallet, Roger Caras, Paris Flammonde, Robert Frankel, February 6, 1968; nebel_1068-1070; 3 reels (Oversize 53)
    - Michael Todd Jr., Sanford Teller, Shirley Herz, February 7, 1968; nebel_1074-1076; 3 reels (Oversize 53, 54)
    - Michael Todd Jr., February 7, 1968; nebel_1077; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 54)
    - "While 6 Million Died" Arthur D. Morse, Seena Hamilton, Noel Behn, Sanford Teller, February 9, 1968; nebel_1082-1084; 3 reels (Oversize 54)
    - "My Friend The Dictator" (repeated 1968 May 19) Cindy Adams, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Bentley Kassal, Terry Garrity, February 10, 1968; nebel_1085-1087; 3 reels (Oversize 54)
    - Dr. S. K. Fineberg, Dr. Howard Miller, February 14, 1968; nebel_1092-1095; 4 reels (Oversize 54, 55)
    - "Welfare" "Sterilization" "Psychiatry" Lester Del Rey, Emerson Coyle, Jay Wishner, Richard Raskin, February 15, 1968; nebel_1097-1099; 3 reels (Oversize 55)
    - Harvey Aronson, Edward Spingarn, Seena Hamilton, Rev. Robert Schrock, February 20, 1968; nebel_1107-1109; 3 reels (Oversize 55)
    - Dr. Alfred Jarrette, Daniel Watts, Al Lottman, Seena Hamilton, David Schulte, February 22, 1968; nebel_1113-1115; 3 reels (Oversize 55)
    - Donald MacLean, Sanford Teller, February 23, 1968; nebel_1118-1120; 3 reels (Oversize 56)
    - "Spofford" (Broadway Play) (aired 1968 April 16) Herman Shulman, Roy Schatt, Terry Garrity, Paris Flammonde, February 27, 1968; nebel_1121-1123; 3 reels (Oversize 56)
    - Jacqueline Susann, Erika Freeman, Terry Garrity, Seena Hamilton, February 27, 1968; nebel_1124-1126; 3 reels (Oversize 56)
    - "Astrology" Katherine De Jersey, Paris Flammonde, Edith Aynes, Samuel Vandervirt, February 28, 1968; nebel_1128-1130; 3 reels (Oversize 56)
    - "Vietnam" Dr. Erika Freeman, Rev. Richard Newhaus, David Schulte, Al Lottman, February 29, 1968; nebel_1132-1135; 4 reels (Oversize 56, 57)
    - "Compulsory Population Control" Dr. Howard Miller, Emerson Coyle, Frederik Pohl, March 1, 1968; nebel_1137-1139; 3 reels (Oversize 57)
    - "Black Market Medicine" (repeated 1968 June 4) Margaret Kreig, Dr. Howard Miller, Seena Hamilton, March 5, 1968; nebel_1141-1143; 3 reels (Oversize 57)
    - "Hypnosis And Cosmic Therapy" Donald Hutchinson, Joseph Lampl, Edith Aynes, March 6, 1968; nebel_1145-1147; 3 reels (Oversize 57)
    - "Pacifism And Catholics" Anthony Denard, Donald MacLean, David Schulte, Al Lottman, March 7, 1968; nebel_1148-1150; 3 reels (Oversize 57)
    - "Incident At Boris Gleb" DeWitt Copp, Dr. Edward Spingarn, Roy Schatt, Paris Flammonde, March 8, 1968; nebel_1152-1154; 3 reels (Oversize 57, 58)
    - "Forensic Pathology" (repeated 1968 April 9; 1968 December 3) Dr. Cyril Wecht, David Schulte, Seena Hamilton, Paris Flammonde, March 9, 1968; nebel_1155-1157; 3 reels (Oversize 58)
    - "Urology" (repeated 1968 May 21) Dr. Philip Roen, March 12, 1968; nebel_1158-1159; 2 reels (Oversize 58)
    - (repeated 1968 May 28; 1968 July 6) Rev. Walter Martin, Al Lottman, Roy Schatt, Will Ousler, March 20, 1968; nebel_1161-1163; 3 reels (Oversize 58)
    - "Coward" (repeated 1968 June 6) Thomas Tiede, Sanford Teller, Robert Cochnar, David Schulte, March 22, 1968; nebel_1166-1168; 3 reels (Oversize 58)
    - "Vietnam" Thomas Tiede, Al Lottman, March 28, 1968; nebel_1169-1171; 1 reel (Oversize 58)
    - "Phones" (Long John Nebel) Lee Evans, April 5, 1968; nebel_1174-1175; 2 reels (Oversize 59)
    - "Food Facts And Fallacies" Dr. Carlton Fredericks, Terry Garrity, Gabe Longo, Eve Green, April 6, 1968; nebel_1177-1180; 4 reels (Oversize 59)
    - "The Claimant" (repeated 1968 July 9) Hollis Alpert, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Robert Cochnar, Sanford Teller, April 12, 1968; nebel_1181-1183; 3 reels (Oversize 59)
    - "The Search For The Girl With The Blue Eyes" (repeated 1968 July 28) Jess Stern, Joseph Lampl, Sanford Teller, Samuel Vandervirt, April 17, 1968; nebel_1185-1187; 3 reels (Oversize 59)
    - "Dreams: Magic Mirror" (aired 1968 August 4) Elsie Sechrist, Paris Flammonde, Roy Schatt, Emerson Coyle, April 18, 1968; nebel_1188-1190; 3 reels (Oversize 59)
    - George Frazier, Bernard Toll, Robert Cochnar, Maxine Brown, April 18, 1968; nebel_1191-1193; 3 reels (Oversize 59)
    - "Cartoons" Robert Dunn, Howard Schneider, Robert Cochnar, Terry Garrity, April 20, 1968; nebel_1195-1197; 3 reels (Oversize 60)
    - "The Unconscious Mind" Dr. Benjamin J. Wolman, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Edward Winter, Terry Garrity, April 24, 1968; nebel_1199-1201; 3 reels (Oversize 60)
    - "Death Of A Hippie (Groovy)" Anthony Lukas, Sanford Teller, Robert Cochnar, April 25, 1968; nebel_1203-1205; 3 reels (Oversize 60)
    - Phil Foster, Danny Crystal, April 26, 1968; nebel_1206-1208; 3 reels (Oversize 60)
    - "Men's Clothes" Phil Foster, Danny Crystal, April 26, 1968; nebel_1209; 1 reel (Oversize 60)
    - "Church And State" (repeated 1968 July 16) Madalyn Murray, Dr. Thomas Molnar, Dr. Emerson Coyle, Will Ousler, April 27, 1968; nebel_1210-1212; 3 reels (Oversize 60)
    - "The Circus" Rudy Bundy, Charles Bauman, Jack Ryan, Rev. Robert Schrock, May 2, 1968; nebel_1216-1218; 3 reels (Oversize 61)
    - "Book Of Days" (repeated 1968 September 1) Rev. Malcom Boyd, Rev. Al Carmines, Rev. Robert Schrock, Eden Gray, May 9, 1968; nebel_1221-1223; 3 reels (Oversize 61)
    - "Psychiatry" Dr. Theodore I. Rubin, Sanford Teller, May 22, 1968; nebel_1229-1231; 3 reels (Oversize 61)
    - "The Progress Of The Protestant" John Haverstick, Rev. Ernest Lilley, Paris Flammonde, May 23, 1968; nebel_1234-1236; 3 reels (Oversize 62)
    - "Biorhythm" (aired 1968 August 18) George Thommen, Seena Hamilton, Eden Grey, David A. Schulte, May 24, 1968; nebel_1237-1239; 3 reels (Oversize 62)
    - "The Body" Dr. Hanna Kapit, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, Seena Hamilton, Terry Garrity, May 25, 1968; nebel_1240-1242; 3 reels (Oversize 62)
    - "Pathway To Spiritual Healing" (aired 1968 August 11) Rev. Noel Street, Dr. Howard Miller, Will Ousler, Paris Flammonde, May 30, 1968; nebel_1243-1245; 3 reels (Oversize 62)
    - "Those Incredible Christians" Dr. Hugh Schonfield, Dr. Howard Miller, Rev. Ernest Lilley, Sanford Teller, June 1, 1968; nebel_1247-1250; 4 reels (Oversize 62)
    - "The Right People" Stephen Birmingham, Sanford Teller, Seena Hamilton, June 5, 1968; nebel_1254-1256; 3 reels (Oversize 63)
    - "Special Counsel: An Inside Report On The Senate Investigations into Communism" (repeated 1968 July 2; 1969 January 2) William A. Rusher, Dr. Thomas Molnar, Bentley Kassal, Sanford Teller, June 8, 1968; nebel_1258-1260; 3 reels (Oversize 63)
    - "The Future Of Conservatism" M. Stanton Evans, Robert Cochner, Frederik Pohl, Albert Lottman, June 13, 1968; nebel_1262-1264A/B; 4 reels (Oversize 63)
    - "McCarthy" (repeated 1968 July 23; 1968 October 9; 1969 April 5), June 14, 1968; nebel_1267-1269; 3 reels (Oversize 63)
    - "Phones" Joseph Lampl, Dr. Howard Miller, June 22, 1968; nebel_1272-1275; 4 reels (Oversize 63, 64)
    - "Parapsychology" Martin Ebon, Selena Hamilton, Paris Flammonde, June 26, 1968; nebel_1277-1280; 4 reels (Oversize 64)
    - "Love" "Depression" (repeated 1969 February 20) Dr. Charles W. Socarides, Seena Hamilton, July 3, 1968; nebel_1284-1287; 4 reels (Oversize 64)
    - "Science Fiction" Fritz Leiber, Frederik Pohl, Lester Del Rey, Sanford Teller, July 4, 1968; nebel_1288-1290A/B; 4 reels (Oversize 64)
    - "Women Alone" (aired 1969 May 4) Isabella Taves, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Al Lottman, Sanford Teller, July 10, 1968; nebel_1292-1295; 4 reels (Oversize 64, 65)
    - Mel Torme, Edward Spingarn, Paris Flammonde, Sanford Teller, July 13, 1968; nebel_1298-1301; 4 reels (Oversize 65)
    - "The New People" Charles E. Winick, Dr. Charles Socarides, Everett Mattlin, Seena Hamilton, July 24, 1968; nebel_1304-1307; 4 reels (Oversize 65)
    - "Women" Isabella Taves, Seena Hamilton, Rea Doerr, July 27, 1968; nebel_1310-1313; 4 reels (Oversize 65, 66)
    - Frederick Weintraub, Paris Flammonde, Roy Schatt, July 31, 1968; nebel_1315-1318; 4 reels (Oversize 66)
    - Dr. Cyril Wecht, Frederik Pohl, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, August 1, 1968; nebel_1320-1323; 4 reels (Oversize 66)
    - "You Could Die Laughing" Joey Adams, Dr. Ed Spingarn, August 9, 1968; nebel_1326-1329; 4 reels (Oversize 66)
    - "Phones" (repeated 1968 September 3) O. John Rogge, Sanford Teller, August 10, 1968; nebel_1331-1333; 3 reels (Oversize 66, 67)
    - Miles Kreuger, Paris Flammonde, Roy Schatt, Dr. Howard Miller, Robert Sherwood, Phyllis Dorne, August 14, 1968; nebel_1335-1338; 4 reels (Oversize 67)
    - "The Experts" Seymour Freidin, Victor Lasky, Al Lottman, August 15, 1968; nebel_1340-1343; 4 reels (Oversize 67)
    - "Phones" Gray Barker, Jim Moseley, Paris Flammonde, Noel Behn, August 16, 1968; nebel_1345-1348; 4 reels (Oversize 67)
    - "Pumphouse Gang" "Electric Kool-Aid Acid Test" Tom Wolfe, Robert Cochnar, Sanford Teller, August 22, 1968; nebel_1349-1352; 4 reels (Oversize 67)
    - "The Jacques Romano Story" Dr. Berthold E. Schwartz, Dr. Howard B. Miller, Paris Flammonde, August 24, 1968; nebel_1354-1357; 4 reels (Oversize 68)
    - "Phones" Seena Hamilton, August 29, 1968; nebel_1358-1360; 3 reels (Oversize 68)
    - Larry King, Dr. Gilbert Holloway, Sanford Teller, August 30, 1968; nebel_1361-1363; 3 reels (Oversize 68)
    - Dr. Gilbert Holloway, Samuel Vandervirt, September 4, 1968; nebel_1364-1367; 4 reels (Oversize 68)
    - Buddy De Franco, Al Caidla, Norman Grossman, Daniel Burgauer, Paris Flammonde, September 6, 1968; nebel_1368-1371; 4 reels (Oversize 68)
    - "How To Live With An Alcoholic" Dr. Jorge Valles, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, Rev. Robert Schrock, September 10, 1968; nebel_1372-1374; 3 reels (Oversize 68, 69)
    - "The American Empire" Amaury De Riencourt, Sanford Teller, Robert Cochnar, Kenneth Knigin, September 11, 1968; nebel_1375-1377; 3 reels (Oversize 69)
    - Dr. Gilbert Holloway, Kenneth Knigin, September 12, 1968; nebel_1378-1381; 4 reels (Oversize 69)
    - "Psychoanalysis Must Go" Dr. James McConnell, Dr. Charles Socarides, Noel Behn, Joel Fisch, September 13, 1968; nebel_1382-1384; 3 reels (Oversize 69)
    - "Men's Fashions" George Frazier III, Bernard Toll, Robert Cochnar, Paris Flammonde, September 18, 1968; nebel_1385-1388; 4 reels (Oversize 69)
    - "Phones" Long John Nebel, September 21, 1968; nebel_1389; 1 reel (Oversize 69)
    - "Letters To A Black Boy" (repeated 1969 July 13) Robert Teague, Daniel H. Watts, Kenneth Knigin, September 21, 1968; nebel_1390-1393; 4 reels (Oversize 69, 70)
    - "Mastery Of Management" (Executive Of The Future) Auren Uris, Al Lottman, David A. Schulte, Seena Hamilton, September 25, 1968; nebel_1394-1397; 4 reels (Oversize 70)
    - James Kavanaugh, Rev. Robert Schrock, September 28, 1968; nebel_1398-1401; 4 reels (Oversize 70)
    - "Sarang" Roger Caras, Paris Flammonde, Stuart And Ariana Hart, October 2, 1968; nebel_1402-1404; 3 reels (Oversize 70)
    - "Worlds Of Fantasy" (repeated 1968 October 13) Lester Del Rey, Paris Flammonde, Samuel Vandervirt, October 3, 1968; nebel_1405-1407; 3 reels (Oversize 70)
    - "The Neighbors Are Scaring My Wolf" Jack Douglas, Reiko Douglas, Joan Crosby, October 4, 1968; nebel_1408-1410; 3 reels (Oversize 70)
    - (aired 1968 December 15) Kingsley Smith, Alan Stolz, Richard Socarides, Simon Salamon, Seena Hamilton, Jeff Segal, October 5, 1968; nebel_1411-1414; 4 reels (Oversize 70, 71)
    - "The Ageless Woman" (aired 1969 March 2) Dr. Sherwin A. Kaufman, Seena Hamilton, October 12, 1968; nebel_1415-1418; 4 reels (Oversize 71)
    - Irwin Greif, James Moseley, Will Ouster, October 18, 1968; nebel_1419-1421; 3 reels (Oversize 71)
    - "The Executive's Wife" Ninki Hart Berger, Rev. Robert Schrock, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Al Lottman, October 19, 1968; nebel_1422-1424; 3 reels (Oversize 71)
    - "Protect Your Life" Judge Sherman Finesilver, David A. Schulte, Kenneth Knigin, October 22, 1968; nebel_1425-1430; 6 reels (Oversize 71)
    - "While The Winds Blew" Msgr. Salvatore J. Adamo, Dr. Thomas Molnar, Gary MacEoin, Rev. Robert Schrock, October 24, 1968; nebel_1431-1433; 3 reels (Oversize 71, 72)
    - Dr. Cyril Wecht, Dr. Howard Miller, Seena Hamilton, October 26, 1968; nebel_1434-1439; 6 reels (Oversize 72)
    - "The Youth Doctors" (repeated 1968 November 24) Patrick McGrady, F. Kay Gardella, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, Seena Hamilton, October 29, 1968; nebel_1440-1443; 4 reels (Oversize 72)
    - Dr. Theodore I. Rubin, Frederik Pohl, Anne Pacurar, October 30, 1968; nebel_1444-1446; 3 reels (Oversize 72)
    - "Meta-Physics: New Dimensions Of The Mind" Anthony Norvell, Will Ousler, Paris Flammonde, November 1, 1968; nebel_1447-1449; 3 reels (Oversize 72)
    - "Religion: Out Or Way Out?" "Marijuana: The Facts, The Truth" Will Ousler, Kenneth Knigin, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, Rev. Robert Schrock, November 2, 1968; nebel_1450-1454; 5 reels (Oversize 72, 73)
    - "The Other Side" (repeated 1968 December 10; 1969 September 18) Bishop James Pike, Diane (Kennedy) Pike, Rev. Robert Schrock, Will Ousler, November 5, 1968; nebel_1455-1457; 3 reels (Oversize 73)
    - Terry Schaertel, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Robert Cochnar, Sanford Teller, November 7, 1968; nebel_1458-1460; 3 reels (Oversize 73)
    - "New Hope For Alcoholics" Dr. Abram Hoffer, Fr. Joseph Ryan, Dr. Hyman Chartock, Seena Hamilton, November 14, 1968; nebel_1461-1464; 4 reels (Oversize 73)
    - "The World's Greatest Jazz Band" Richard Gibson, November 15, 1968; nebel_1465; 1 reel (Oversize 73)
    - "Eat Drink, Be Merry, And Live Longer" (repeated 1969 January 5) Dr. Harry J. Johnson, Bentley Kassal, Seena Hamilton, November 15, 1968; nebel_1466-1468; 3 reels (Oversize 73)
    - "Jazz" Richard Gibson, November 15, 1968; nebel_1469; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 73)
    - "The Art Of Negotiating" Gerard Wierenberg, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Sanford Teller, November 16, 1968; nebel_1470-1475; 6 tapes (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 73, 74)
    - "Zen Macrobiotic Cooking" (Reels 3 & 4 aired 1968 December 1) Michael Abehsera, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, Eden Gray; and "World's Greatest Jazz Band, At Riverboat" Dick Gibson, Danny Burgauer, November 19, 1968; nebel_1476-1479; 4 reels (Oversize 74)
    - (repeated 1968 December 22) O. John Rogge, Manuel N. Zapata, Dr. Edward Spingarn, November 23, 1968; nebel_1480-1482; 3 reels (Oversize 74)
    - "Photography" Karl Breford, Philip Leonian, Sandy Teller, November 26, 1968; nebel_1483-1485; 3 reels (Oversize 74)
    - "Social Security" (repeated 1969 January 7) Charles S. Ferber, Celeste A. Hemingson, Seena Hamilton, November 30, 1968; nebel_1486-1490; 5 reels (Oversize 74)
    - "American Woman" Nerin E. Gun, Paris Flammonde, Seena Hamilton, David A. Schulte, December 4, 1968; nebel_1491-1494; 4 reels (Oversize 74, 75)
    - "Tune In Tomorrow" Mary Jane Higby, Paris Flammonde, Roy Schatt, Dr. Edward Spingarn, John Powers, December 5, 1968; nebel_1495-1497; 3 reels (Oversize 75)
    - "Faces People Wear" Rev. Charles Di Salvo, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Seena Hamilton, Rev. Robert Schrock, December 6, 1968; nebel_1498-1500; 3 reels (Oversize 75)
    - "Women" Daniel Watts, Kenneth Knigin, December 7, 1968; nebel_1501-1504; 4 reels (Oversize 75)
    - Harry Trefflich, Paris Flammonde, December 13, 1968; nebel_1505-1507; 3 reels (Oversize 75)
    - Kenneth Knigin, Seena Hamilton, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, December 14, 1968; nebel_1508-1513; 6 reels (Oversize 75)
    - "Birth And Death" Arthur and Evelyn Barron, Sanford Teller, Robert Cochnar, Thomas Cassidy, December 19, 1968; nebel_1514-1516; 3 reels (Oversize 76)
    - "Allergies" "Famine And Overpopulation" "Transplants" (repeated 1969 March 16) Dr. Harry Swartz, Seena Hamilton, December 20, 1968; nebel_1517-1519; 3 reels (Oversize 76)
    - "Encyclopedia Of Humor" Joey Adams, Al Lottman, December 21, 1968; nebel_1520-1522; 3 reels (Oversize 76)
    - "The Longest Street: A Memoir" (repeated 1969 February 9) Louis Sobol, Sanford Teller, December 27, 1968; nebel_1523-1525; 3 reels (Oversize 76)
    - "Marketing" David J. Rachman, Al Lottman, Sanford Teller, January 3, 1969; nebel_1526-1528; 3 reels (Oversize 76)
    - John Reeves, Paris Flammonde, Samuel Vandervirt, January 4, 1969; nebel_1529-1532; 4 reels (Oversize 76)
    - "Phones" Kay Gardella, Kenneth Knigin, January 9, 1969; nebel_1533-1535; 3 reels (Oversize 76, 77)
    - Arnold Bergier, Seena Hamilton, Jay Wishner, January 10, 1969; nebel_1536-1538; 3 reels (Oversize 77)
    - "The Kennedy Conspiracy" Paris Flammonde, Fred Pohl, Dr. Howard Miller, January 11, 1969; nebel_1539-1542; 4 reels (Oversize 77)
    - "Ecumenism or New Reformation" Dr. Thomas Molnar, Joseph Scheuer, Rev. David Poling, January 15, 1969; nebel_1543-1545; 3 reels (Oversize 77)
    - Phil Foster, Al Lottman, January 16, 1969; nebel_1546-1548; 3 reels (Oversize 77)
    - Dr. Klaus Westphal, James Barnet, Sanford Teller, Fred W. Weitz, January 17, 1969; nebel_1549-1551; 3 reels (Oversize 77)
    - Dr. Erika Freeman. Sanford Teller, Jay Wishner, January 23, 1969; nebel_1552-1554; 3 reels (Oversize 77, 78)
    - (repeated 1969 April 8) Victor Lasky, Paris Flammonde, Al Lottman, January 24, 1969; nebel_1555-1557; 3 reels (Oversize 78)
    - "Urology And Gynecology" Dr. Philip R. Roen, Dr. Sherman A. Kaufman, Kenneth Knigin, January 25, 1969; nebel_1558-1561; 4 reels (Oversize 78)
    - Milton Caniff, Kenneth Knigin, Al Lottman, January 29, 1969; nebel_1562-1564; 3 reels (Oversize 78)
    - "The Last Years Of The Church" (repeated 1969 March 23) Rev. David Poling, Will Ousler, Paris Flammonde, Rev. Robert Schrock, February 1, 1969; nebel_1565-1567; 3 reels (Oversize 78)
    - "Public Relations" Sanford Teller, Thomas Cassidy, Robert Carson, February 5, 1969; nebel_1568-1570; 3 reels (Oversize 78)
    - "Spiritual Healing And Reincarnation" (repeated 1969 April 1) Rev. Noel Street, Paris Flammonde, Stewart Robb, Kenneth Knigin, February 6, 1969; nebel_1571-1573; 3 reels (Oversize 78, 79)
    - "Snakes: The Keeper And The Kept" (repeated 1969 May 11) Carl F. Kauffeld, Paris Flammonde, Roy Schatt, Samuel Vandervirt, February 8, 1969; nebel_1574-1576; 3 reels (Oversize 79)
    - "The Vitamin Pioneers" (repeated 1969 April 13) Herbert Baily, Dr. S. K. Fineberg, February 12, 1969; nebel_1577-1579; 3 reels (Oversize 79)
    - Carol Reed, Dr. Edward Spingarn, Seena Hamilton, Albert Lottman, February 18, 1969; nebel_1580-1582; 3 reels (Oversize 79)
    - (repeated 1969 March 18) John Keel, Sanford Teller, Paris Flammonde, Lilian Freedman, Stuart Daniels, February 19, 1969; nebel_1583-1585; 3 reels (Oversize 79)
    - Dr. Cyril Wecht, February 22, 1969; nebel_1586; 1 reel (1/4"x1200') (Oversize 79)
    - (repeated 1969 July 20) Leeham Lowin, Sanford Teller, Robert Carson, February 28, 1969; nebel_1587-1589; 3 reels (Oversize 79)
    - "Hex" (repeated 1969 July 6) Arthur H. Lewis, Paris Flammonde, Will Ousler, Kenneth Knigin, March 1, 1969; nebel_1590-1592; 3 reels (Oversize 79, 80)
    - "Separation of Church And State" (repeated 1969 May 28) Madalyn Murray, Rev. Robert Schrock, Seena Hamilton, March 6, 1969; nebel_1593-1595; 3 reels (Oversize 80)
    - (repeated 1969 March 13) Susan Brownmiller, Dr. Thomas Molnar, Albert Lottman, Seena Hamilton, March 7, 1969; nebel_1596-1598; 3 reels (Oversize 80)
    - "Common Sense About Psychoanalysis" Dr. Rudolph Wittenberg, Joel Fisch, Dr. Hanna Kapit, March 8, 1969; nebel_1599-1601; 3 reels (Oversize 80)
    - "Houdini: The Untold Story" (repeated 1969 June 8) Milbourne Christopher, Roy Schatt, March 12, 1969; nebel_1602-1604; 3 reels (Oversize 80)
    - (repeated 1969 June 10) Jean Shepherd, Sam Vandervirt, March 15, 1969; nebel_1605-1606; 2 reels (Oversize 80)
    - "How Could She Do That? A Study Of The Female Criminal" (repeated 1969 July 27) Edith Derham, Dr. Hanna Kapit, Don MacLean, March 20, 1969; nebel_1608-1610; 3 reels (Oversize 80)
    - Harvey Stone, Paris Flammonde, Kenneth Knigin, Norman Lear, March 21, 1969; nebel_1611-1613; 3 reels (Oversize 80, 81)
    - (repeated 1969 April 4) Kenneth Knigin, Jay Wishner, March 25, 1969; nebel_1614-1616; 3 reels (Oversize 81)
    - (repeated 1969 April 10) Jack Cumley, Al Lottman, March 28, 1969; nebel_1617-1619; 3 reels (Oversize 81)
    - Jack Banning Jr., Paris Flammonde, Roy Coughlin, Kenneth Knigin, April 5, 1969; nebel_1620-1622; 3 reels (Oversize 81)
    - "Phones" Ken Knigin, April 5, 1969; nebel_1623-1624; 2 reels (Oversize 81)
    - "Voyage To Atlantis" James W. Mayor, Frederik Pohl, Sanford Teller, April 10, 1969; nebel_1625-1627; 3 reels (Oversize 81)
    - "Jim Lee's Chinese Cook Book" (repeated 1969 April 29) Jim Lee, Isabella Lee, Al Lottman, April 12, 1969; nebel_1628-1630; 3 reels (Oversize 81)
    - "Phones" (3:30-6:00 AM) Jules L. Spodek, April 12, 1969; nebel_1631-1633; 3 reels (Oversize 81, 82)
    - "Phones" (-6:00 AM) Ken Knigin, April 19, 1969; nebel_1634-1635; 2 reels (Oversize 82)
    - "Away From it All" (repeated 1969 June 15) Sloan Wilson, Sanford Teller, April 23, 1969; nebel_1636-1638; 3 reels (Oversize 82)
    - "Stealing" Val Moolman, Al Lottman, Alan Cornet, Kenneth Knigin, April 24, 1969; nebel_1639-1641; 3 reels (Oversize 82)
    - "The Palace" (repeated 1969 May 1) Marian Spitzer, Roy Schatt, Sanford Teller, April 25, 1969; nebel_1642-1644; 3 reels (Oversize 82)
    - (repeated 1969 May 2) Robert Carson, Sanford Teller, Al Lottman, Kenneth Knigin, April 26, 1969; nebel_1645-1648; 4 reels (Oversize 82)